<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="umrah_first">Umrah (the ‘Minor Hajj’) is a Sunnah and can be performed anytime of the year except for the five days of Hajj . During this time, it is Makruh Tahrimi to perform Umrah.</string>
    <string name="virtues_of_umrah">VIRTUES OF UMRAH</string>
    <string name="farz_act_umrah">FARDH ACTS OF UMRAH</string>
    <string name="umrah">UMRAH</string>
    <string name="virtues_of_umrah_desc"><b>1</b>. One Umrah is a cleanser for the sins committed between it and another Umrah. (Bukhari, Muslim)\n2. To perform one Umrah in Ramadhan is equivalent to a Hajj . In another narration, it is equivalent to Hajj performed with the prophet.(Muslim)\n3. The performers of Hajj and Umrah are representatives (of the order) of Allah. If they call Him, He answers them and if they seek His forgiveness He forgives them. (Ibn Majah)</string>
    <string name="farz_act_umrah_desc"><b>1</b>. Ihraam (i.e. The garments, with Niyyah and Talbiyah).\n<b>2</b>. Tawaaf (with Niyyah).\n <b>The Wajib acts of Umrah </b>:\n<b>3</b>. Sa’i (walking between Safa and Marwah).\n<b>4</b>. Halaq or Qasr .</string>
    <string name="prior_to_departure">PRIOR TO DEPARTURE</string>
    <string name="prior_to_departure_desc"><b>1</b>. Before leaving, perform two Raka’at Nafl in one’s own home. On completing the two Raka’at, firstly thank Allah for the favour which He has bestowed upon us by granting us the understanding and the opportunity to perform this duty.\n\n<b>2</b>. Thereafter, one must make Du’a to Allah, and ask Him to make the journey easy, and to make it full of benefits and blessings, and that He keeps you safe from the evil of Shaytan and Nafs. Also make Du’a that He gives one the opportunity to use one’s time in those actions which will bring His Pleasure and that He accepts the Umrah.\n\n<b>3</b>. Now starts the journey. Throughout this journey one must perform the five Fardh Salaah regularly and punctually . We all must ensure that we do not cause harm or difficulty to anyone. But rather, one should be of assistance to any needy person, and not waste time in futile pursuits. Remember to spend as much time as possible in learning, teaching, worship and remembrance of Allah as this is the place for it.</string>

    <!-- <string name="ihram_desc_1"><b>1</b>. Prior to entering the Miqat, try to perform Ghusl, otherwise Wudhu will suffice.Thereafter,wear the Ihraam,two white sheets, one for the upper and one for the lower part of the body. At this point, men may apply Itr (perfume). The women should keep all their body covered in their normal (Islamic) clothing, except the face.\n\n <b>2</b>. With the head covered Perform two Raka’at Nafl Salaah with the intention of ihraam. Recite Surah Al Kafirun in the first Raka’at and Surah Al Ikhlas in the second Raka’at, it is not necessary to read these particular verses, but traditions have recorded that the prophet (pbuh) had read them at this particular moment. <b>3</b>. On completing the two Raka’at, remove the headgear and make Niyyah of Umrah saying:</string> -->
    <string name="ihram_desc_1">Prior to entering the Miqat, try to perform Ghusl, otherwise Wudhu will suffice.Thereafter,wear the Ihraam,two white sheets, one for the upper and one for the lower part of the body. At this point, men may apply Itr (perfume). The women should keep all their body covered in their normal (Islamic) clothing, except the face.</string>
    <string name="niyyah_making">With the head covered perform two Raka’at Nafl Salaah with the intention of Ihraam(Salatul Ihram). Recite Surah Al Kafirun in the first Raka’at and Surah Al Ikhlas in the second Raka’at, it is not necessary to read these particular verses, but traditions have recorded that the prophet (pbuh) had read them at this particular moment.\nOn completing the two Raka’at, remove the headgear and make Niyyah of Umrah saying:</string>
    <string name="enter_iharam_state">The state of Ihraam is entered by the following:\n<b>(1)</b> Making Niyyah.\n<b>(2)</b> Recitating of Talbiyah.</string>
    <string name="ihram_niyyah">EHRAM NIYYAH</string>
    <string name="dua_umrah_niyyat">ALLA HUMMA INNI URIDUL UMRATA FAYAS-SIRHA LI WA TAQABBALHA MINNI.</string>
    <string name="umrah_niyyat">UMRAH NIYYAH(Intention)</string>
    <string name="umrah_niyyat_meaning">“O Allah, I intend to perform Umrah. Make it easy for me and accept it from me”.</string>
    <string name="make_dual_after_salatul_Ihram">And make the following Du’a</string>
    <string name="dua_after_niyyah">DU’A FOR INTENTION FOR HAJJ AND UMRAH</string>
    <string name="dua_after_niyyah_pronounce">ALLAHUMMA INNI URIDUL UMRATA WAL HAJJA FAYASSIR HUMA LI WA TAQABALHUMA MINNI, LABBAYKA BIHAJJATIW WA UMRATIN.</string>
    <string name="dua_after_niyyah_meaning">"O Allah! I intend Umrah and Hajj. Make them easy for me and accept them from me. I am present for Hajj and Umrah".</string>
    <string name="dua_after_salatul_ihram_pronounce">ALLAHUMMA INNI AS ALUKA RIDAKA WAL JANNATA WA A UDHUBIKA MIN GHADABIKA WANNAR.</string>
    <string name="dua_after_salatul_ihram_meaning">"O Allah! I seek Your pleasure and heaven. And I seek Your refuge from Your anger and the Fire".</string>
    <string name="talbiyah">TALBIYA</string>
    <string name="talbiyah_instr">Then read the following Du’a (known as <b>TALBIYA</b>) thrice.\n(<u>Men</u> should recite these words <u>aloud</u>, and <u>women</u> should do so <u>softly</u>)</string>
    <string name="talbiyah_pronounce">LABBAYK. ALLAHUMMA LABBAYK. LABBAYKA LA SHARIKA LAKA LABBAYK. INNAL HAMDA WAN-NIMATA LAKA WAL MULK. LA SHARIKA LAK. </string>
    <string name="talbiyah_meaning">“Here I am at Your Service, O Lord, here I am. Here I am, no partner do You have, here I am. Truly, the Praise and the Favour is Yours, and the Sovereignty. No partner do You have”.</string>
    <string name="now_recite">Now, recite DURUD and continue making DU’A for as long as possible.</string>
    <string name="ihram_impermissible">IMPERMISSIBLE ACTS WHILST IN IHRAAM</string>
    <string name="ihram_impermissible_text"><b>1</b>. It is strictly prohibited to indulge in kissing, embracing, sexual intercourse and even talking about sex. Refrain from all those acts which are within this classification. \n\n<b>2</b>. It is prohibited and even more harmful to indulge in those acts which Allah has ordained Haram e.g. Foul or dirty language, sin, fighting, etc. \n\n<b>3</b>. It is Haram to hunt animals or to even help anyone perform this act; even the killing of an ant or even a louse is prohibited. \n\n<b>4</b>. One must refrain from using scents, perfumes, perfumed oils, soaps, shampoos or any items of fragrance; on the body and even the clothes. \n\n<b>5</b>. It is prohibited to shave or trim hair from any part of the body; it is also prohibited to clip the nails. \n\n<b>6</b>. It is impermissible for men to use sewn or stitched clothes. \n\n<b>7</b>. It is prohibited for men to wear any such footwear that covers the central bone of the upper part of the feet. \n\n<b>8</b>. Men must not cover their heads or faces. \n\n<b>9</b>. Women, in the presence of men, must cover their faces in such a manner that the covering does not touch it, wearing a baseball type cap under the covering can be helpful. \n\n<b>10</b>. Do not cause harm to any Muslim neither verbally nor physically.</string>
    <string name="ihram_permissible">ACTS ALLOWED WHILST IN THE STATE OF IHRAAM</string>
    <string name="ihram_permissible_text"><b>1</b>. It is permissible to use an umbrella or any object for shade, as long as it does not rest on the head.\n\n <b>2</b>. Any such item which is not clothing, provided it is for a valid reason, is permitted.\n\n <b>3</b>. It is permited to wash/change one’s garments, as well as to wash one’s hair and body without using scented soap.\n\n<b>4</b>.The natural shedding of hair due to washing is not an issue of concern.\n\n <b>5</b>. It is permissible to cover the body, including the feet while sleeping with any garment or blanket. (Do not however, cover the head or face).\n\n <b>6</b>. It is permitted to use a toothbrush/miswak to clean the teeth.\n\n <b>7</b>. There is no harm in carrying something on the head if the need arises.</string>
    <string name="dua_outside_makkah">DU’A OUTSIDE MAKKAH</string>
    <string name="dua_outside_makkah_pronounce">"ALLAHUMMA ALBALADU BALADUKA WAL BAYTU BAYTUKA JI'TU ATLUBU RAMATAKA WA ALZIMU TA'ATAKA MUTTABI`AL LI'AMRIKA RADIYAN BI QUDRATIKA MUS TASLIMAL-LI AMRIKA AS'ALUKA MAS ALATAL-MUDTARRI ILAYKA AL MUSHFIKI MIN`ADHABIKA KHA'IFAN LI`UQUBATIKA AN TASTAQBILANI BI`AFWIKA WA AN TATAJAWAZA ANNI BIRAHMATIKA WA AN TUD KHILANI JAN-NATAKA.</string>
    <string name="dua_outside_makkah_meaning">\"O Allah! This city (Makkah) is Your city. And this house (Ka’bah) is Your house. I come seeking Your mercy, and holding fast unto Your obedience, subservient to Your order, pleased with Your decree and accepting Your command. I beg of You; in the begging manner of the distressed, who dread Your punishment, and fear Your wrath; that You confront me with Your pardon, and that You encompass me with Your mercy, and that You enter me into Your (prepared) Heaven\".</string>
    <string name="upon_arrival">UPON ARRIVAL AT THE HOLY CITY</string>
    <string name="upon_arrival_inst">Upon donning the Ihraam, you should engage yourself in the remembrance of Allah, Istighfar and recitation of the Talbiyah until you reach Makkah.\n\n <b>1</b>. Enter the holy city of Makkah with true respect and humility whilst reciting the Talbiyah.\n\n<b>2</b>.Make arrangements and immediately go to the sacred Masjid which is known as Al Masjidul Haram. Where upon enter the Masjid with utmost humility, consciousness of the Greatness of Allah and mindfulness of the sacredness of the place.\n\n <b>3</b>. When entering the Masjid, put your right foot in the Masjid and say either of the following:</string>
    <string name="dua_entering_masjid">DU\'A ON ENTERING MASJID AL HARAM</string>
    <string name="dua_entering_masjid_pronounce">BISMILLAHI WAS-SALATU WAS-SALAMU ALA RASULIL-LAH.\nALLAHUM-MAFTA LI ABWABA RAHMATIK.</string>
    <string name="dua_entering_masjid_meaning">“In the name of Allah. May the Peace and Salutations (of Allah) be upon the Messenger of Allah. O Allah, open for me the doors of Your Mercies”.</string>
    <string name="dua_leaving_masjid">DU’A ON LEAVING AL MASJIDUL HARAM</string>
    <string name="dua_leaving_masjid_pronounce">BISMILLAHI ALLAHUMMA SALLI ALA MUHAMMADIN, ALLAHUMMA INNI ASALUKA MIN FADLIK.</string>
    <string name="dua_leaving_masjid_meaning">\"In the name of Allah. O Allah! Send Your salutation upon Muhammad. O Allah! I ask You for Your grace\".</string>
    <string name="on_seeing_kaba">When you see Ka’bah, say the following thrice:</string>
    <string name="dua_seeing_kabah">DU\'A SEEING KABAH</string>
    <string name="dua_seeing_kabah_pronounce">ALLAHU AKBAR. LA ILAHA ILLAL-LAH</string>
    <string name="dua_seeing_kabah_meaning">\"Allah is the greatest. There are none worthy of worship but Allah\".</string>
    <string name="after_dua">Thereafter, recite Durud and make Du’a whilst standing and facing the Ka’bah.</string>
    <string name="dua_on_sigting_heading">DU’A ON SIGHTING THE KA’BAH</string>
    <string name="dua_on_sigting_pronounce">"ALLAHUMMA ANTAS-SALAMU WA MINKAS-SALAMU TABARAKTA YA DHALJALAALI WAL IKRAM ALLAHUMMA ZID HADHAL BAYTA TASHRIFAW WA TA'ZIMAW WATAKRIMAW WA MAHABATAN WA ZID MAN SHAR-RAFAHU WA KARRAMAHU MIMMAN HAJJAHU AWI`TAMARAHU TASHRIFAW WA TA'ZIMAW WA TAKRIMAW WA BIRRA.</string>
    <string name="dua_on_sigting_meaning">\"O Allah! You are peace, from You comes peace, elevated are You, O Possessor of majesty and clemency. O Allah! Increase this House (Ka’bah) in dignity, honour, nobility and awe. And increase those who honour and sanctify it by performing Hajj and Umrah, in dignity, honour, nobility and piety\".</string>
    <string name="important"><b>IMPORTANT</b>: This short moment is extremely precious, as whatever Du’a is made, it is certainly accepted by Allah. Thus lengthen the Du’a at this juncture as much as possible.\n\n One must not forget to make this Du’a:\n\n <b>“O Allah, when you take me away from this world, take me in the state of Imaan. O Allah, enter me into Jannah without any account. O Allah, accept all my Du’a and keep me steadfast on Deen”</b>.\n\n One should also make Du’a for the Muslim Ummah in general at this time, that Allah! help all those who are suffering\n\n <b>Mas’alah</b>: A woman in the state of menstruation or post-natal bleeding must not enter the Masjid.</string>
    <string name="tawaf">Tawaf</string>
    <string name="tawaf_intro">Tawaf which is a Fardh part of Umrah must be performed. During Tawaf, engage in the remembrance of Allah and Du’a. The recital of the holy Qur’an is also advisable. Be mindful that the voice is not raised as this can cause disturbance to others.\n\n <b>1</b>. Proceed towards the corner of the Ka’bah in which the Black Stone (Al-Hajarul Aswad) is placed.\n\n <b>2</b>. Looking from the Ka’bah towards the walls of the Mataf (the opening in which the Ka’bah is), you will see a green light diagonally in line with on of the corners of the Ka’bah. In this is Al-Hajarul Aswad. Another sign for locating it is that at present it is located in that corner of the Ka’bah facing one minaret; (the rest of the three corners face corners of two minarets. The floor is also marked with a black /brown line which stretches from Al Hajarul Aswad).\n\n <b>3</b>. Upon reaching this corner, making Tlbiyah stand in such a manner that it (Al Hajarul Aswad) lies straight in front. Males should uncover the right shoulder.\n\n <b>4</b>. Stop Talbiyah and make Niyyah (which is Fardh) to perform Tawaaf.</string>
    <string name="dua_intention_tawaf">"DU’A FOR INTENTION FOR TAWAAF</string>
    <string name="dua_intention_tawaf_pronounce">"ALLAHUMMA INNI URIDU TAWAFA BAYTIKAL HARAMI FAYASSIRHU LI WA TAQABBALHU MINNI SAB'ATA ASHWATIN LILLAHI TA-ALA</string>
    <string name="dua_intention_tawaf_meaning">\"O Allah! I intend to perform tawaaf (circumnavigation) of Your sanctified House, make it easy for me and accept it from me. (I perform) seven rounds for Allah, the exalted\".</string>
    <string name="proceed_to_black_line"><b>5</b>. Proceed to and stand on the black line (which indicates that you are directly in line with Al Hajarul Aswad) keeping one’s face and chest in it’s direction.\n\n <b>6</b>. Raise your hands up to the ears, not touching them and palms facing Al Hajarul Aswad saying:</string>
    <string name="dua_facing_hajarul_aswad">"Du'a facing Al Hajarul Aswad</string>
    <string name="dua_facin_hajarul_aswad_pronounce">BISMILLAHI ALLAHU AKBAR. WALIL-LAHI HAMD</string>
    <string name="dua_facin_hajarul_aswad_meaning">“In the Name of Allah, Allah is the Greatest and all praise is for Allah”.</string>
    <string name="istilam">Istilam</string>
    <string name="place_both_palm"><b>7</b>. Place both palms on Al Hajarul Aswad and gently kiss it. If kissing is not possible, then merely touch it with one hand or both hands. If this too is not possible raise your hands (palms facing Al Hajarul Aswad) and after saying the following kiss them.</string>
    <string name="dua_before_kissing_palm">Du\'a before kissing palm</string>
    <string name="dua_before_kissing_palm_pronounce">BISMILLAHI ALLAHU AKBAR</string>
    <string name="dua_before_kissing_palm_meaning">“In the Name of Allah, Allah is the Greatest”.</string>
    <string name="this_is_known_as_istilam">This is known as Istilam. (Under no circumstances should anyone be caused difficulty to get to it). It is to be performed after each circuit while standing on the black / brown line facing Al Hajarul Aswad.</string>
    <string name="now_moving_towards_the_right"><b>8</b>. Now moving towards the right, and keeping the Ka\’bah on the left one must walk around the Ka\’bah anti-clockwise until you return to Al Hajarul Aswad. Here, perform Istilam. One circuit has now been completed. Complete seven circuits in this manner to complete the Tawaaf.</string>
    <string name="tawaf_adiyah">TAWAAF ADIYAH(Du\'a during Tawaf)</string>
    <string name="tawaf_adiya_desc"><u><b>Mas\’alah</b></u>: There is no fixed set of Adiyah(Supplications) for Tawaaf.\nOne should make Du\’a for the fulfilment of one’s needs of this world and the hereafter.\nHere are few Adiyah(Supplications) that can be read during Tawaaf, try to memorise some as it may be difficult to read these in the crowd.</string>
    <string name="dua_rabbana_atina">Du\'a Rabbana Atina…</string>
    <string name="dua_rabbana_atina_pronounce">RABBANA ATINA FID-DUNYA HASANATAW WA FIL AKHIRATI HASANATAW WA QINA ADHABAN NAR.</string>
    <string name="dua_rabbana_atina_meaning">\"O all-sustaining being! Grant us all good in this world, and all good in the hereafter, and save us from the fire\".</string>
    <string name="dua_subhanallahi">Du\'a SUBHANAL-LAHI…</string>
    <string name="dua_subhanallahi_pronounce">SUBHANAL-LAHI WAL HAMDU LILLAHI WA LA ILAHA ILLAL-LAHU WAL-LAHU AKBAR. WALA HAWLA WA LA QUWATA ILLA BILLAHIL ALIYUL AZIM.</string>
    <string name="dua_subhanallahi_meaning">\"Glorified is Allah. All praise be to Allah. There is no god but Allah. Allah is the greatest. There is no power, no might besides that of Allah, the High, the Exalted\".</string>
    <string name="dua_ya_rabbal_baiti">Du\'a ya rabbal baiti…</string>
    <string name="dua_ya_rabbal_baiti_pronounce">YA RABBAL-BAYTIL-ATIQI ATIQ RIQABANA WARIQABA ABAA INA WA UMMAHATINA MINANIR.</string>
    <string name="dua_ya_rabbal_baiti_meaning">\"O Lord of the this venerable house, free us and our fathers and mothers from the Fire\".</string>
    <string name="on_completing_seventh_circuit"><b>9</b>. On completing the seventh circuit, perform Istilam and proceed to Maqam Ibrahim and offer two Raka’at Salaah (this is Wajib). It is a Sunnah to recite Surah Al Kafirun in the first Raka’at and Surah Al Ikhlas in the second Raka’at. Thereafter engage yourself in Du’a.</string>
    <string name="in_no_place_available"><b>NOTE</b>: If there is no place available at Maqam Ibrahim, it is sufficient to perform the two Raka’at anywhere within the holy Masjid.</string>
    <string name="proceed_towards_the_well"><b>10</b>. Now proceed towards the well of Zamzam and facing the direction of Ka’bah, drink some of its water (if one is not fasting). Also the face and arms can be washed with it. Nowadays access to the well is not possible, so drinking from any of the Zamzam water barrels is sufficient.</string>

    <!-- ================================================ Sai ====================================================== -->
    <string name="sai">SA\'I</string>
    <string name="sai_meaning">To walk between Safa and Marwah seven times (i.e. From Safa to Marwah four times and back thrice). It is performed walking, except for a portion in the middle marked by green lights, where in the pace is quickened to a fast walk (not run).</string>
    <string name="sai_start_desc"><b>1</b>.Before starting Sa\'i, perform Istilam of Hajr-e-Aswad again and then proceed to Safa.\n\n <b>2</b>. Climb Safa and face Ka’bah and make Niyyah for Sa’i.\n\n <b>3</b>. Keep facing the Ka’bah, and raise both hands up to the shoulders in the manner of Du’a. Then say thrice the follwing:</string>
    <string name="while_facing_kaba">facing the Ka\’ba and hand raised in du\'a manner</string>
    <string name="recite_durud"><b>4</b>. Recite Durud and make Du’a for the fulfilment of your own correct wishes and the wishes of others also. Remain engaged in Du’a for as long as possible, for this is also a place where Du’a is accepted.</string>
    <string name="you_must_now_proceed"><b>5</b>.You must now proceed at a walking pace towards Marwah. Whilst walking between Safa and Marwah you should engage your time in Dhikr and Du\’a.\n\n <b>6</b>. When you reach the green lights, you must quicken your pace and march briskly until you reach the other set of green lights. Thereafter, you should resume the normal speed of walking till you reach Marwah. Women, should walk at their normal pace throughout.</string>
    <string name="upon_completion_of_sai">Upon the completion of Sa\’i, either shave or trim the hair of the entire head. Shaving is much more virtuous, but if one trims the hair then it must be in a manner that at least one inch of each hair is trimmed. Women should trim just over an inch of their hair. It is not permissible for them to shave their heads, nor excessively shorten their hair.</string>
    <string name="upon_shaving">Upon the shaving or cutting of the hair, the Umrah has been completed and all the regulations of the Ihraam will end. Now we must make Du\’a  to Allah to accept our Umrah and bestow us with its blessings.</string>
    <string name="dua_at_safa">DU\'A AT SAFA</string>
    <string name="dua_at_safa_pronounce">INNAS-SAFA WAL MARWATA MIN SHA-AA\'IRIL-LAH. LAILAHA ILLALLAHU - ALLAHU AKBAR. ALLAHU AKBAR. ALLAHU AKBAR. WA LILLAHIL HAMD. AL HAMDU LILLAHI \`ALA MA HADANA, AL-HAMDU LILLAHI \`ALA MA AWLANA, AL-HAMDU LILLAHI \`ALA MA ALHAMANA. AL HAMDU LILLAHIL-LADHI HADANA LIHADHA WA MA KUNNA LINAHTADIYA LAWLA AN HADANAL-LAH. LA ILAHA ILLALLAHU WAHDAHU LA SHARIKA LAHU LAHUL-MULKU WA LAHUL-HAMDU. YUH-YI WA YUMITU WA HUWA \`ALA KULLI SHAY\’IN QADIR. LA ILAHA ILLALLAHU WAHDAHU, WA NASARA \`ABDAHU, WA HAZAMAL-AHZABA WAHDAHU. LA ILAHA ILLALLAHU WAL NABUDU ILLA IYYAHU MUKHLISINA LAHUD-DINA WALAW KARIHAL KAFIRUN. ALLAHUMMA KAMA HADAYTANA LIL-ISLAMI AS-\’ALUKA AN LA TANZI\`AHU MINNI HATTA TAWAFFANI WA ANA MUSLIMUN. SUBHANAL-LAHI WAL-HAMDU LILLAHI WALA ILAHA ILLALLAHU ALLAHU-AKBAR. WA LA-HAWLA WA LA QUWATA ILLA BILLAHIL \`ALIYIL \`ADHIM. ALLAHUMMA SALLI WASALLIM \`ALA SAYYADINA MUHAMMADIN WA \`ALA ILIHA WA SABBIHI WA ATBA \`IHI ILA YAWMID-DIN. WA SALAMUN \`ALAL-MURSALIN. WAL-\'HAMDU LILLAHI RABBIL-\`ALAMIN.</string>
    <string name="dua_at_safa_meaning">\""Indeed the mountains of Safa and Marwah are amongst the signs of Allah. There is no god besides Allah. Allah is the greatest. Allah is the greatest. Allah is the greatest. For Allah is all praise. All praise be for Allah, Who has guided us. All praise be for Allah, Who has befriended us. All praise be for Allah, Who has inspired us (and given us understanding). All praise be for Allah, Who has guided us to do this (Hajj/Umrah), as we would not have found the right way if He had not guided us. There is none worthy of worship besides Allah, who is alone and has no partner (equal). For Him is sovereignty and for Him is all praise. He gives life and causes death, and He has power over everything. There is none worthy of worship but Allah, who is alone, who has helped His servant, and who single-handedly has destroyed nations. There is none worthy of worship besides Allah, who we worship none besides, sincerely in faith, be it to the disliking of the apostates. Like how You have guided me to Islam, I ask that You never let it slip away from me, and until my death I remain a Muslim. Glorified is Allah. All praise be to Allah. There is none worthy of worship besides Allah. Allah is the greatest. There is no power, no might besides that belonging to Allah, the Exalted the Mighty. O Allah! Bestow Your salutations and peace upon our leader, Muhammad (PBUH), and upon his household, his companions and his followers, until the last day. Peace be upon all the sent ones (prophets) , and praise be to Allah the Lord of the worlds\"".</string>
    <string name="dua_between_safa_marwah">DU\’A BETWEEN SAFA- MARWAH AND AT MARWAH</string>
    <string name="dua_between_safa_marwah_1_pronounce">ALLAHUMMA INNI ASALUKA MINAL-KHAYRI KULLIHI \`A-JILIHI WA JILIHI MA \`ALIMTU MINHU WA MA LAM A\`-LAM.</string>
    <string name="dua_between_safa_marwah_1_meaning">\"O Allah! I ask You for all what is good, of the present and future, whether I know of it or not\".</string>
    <string name="dua_between_safa_marwah_2_pronounce">ALLAHUMMAH-DINA ILAL HAQQI WAJ-\`ALNA MIN AHLIHI WAN-SURNI BIH.</string>
    <string name="dua_between_safa_marwah_2_meaning">\"O Allah! Guide us to the truth, make us from truth’s upholders, and help us in (upholding) it\".</string>

</resources>