<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="fourth_kalima_1">FOURTH KALIMA 1</string>
    <string name="fourth_kalima_2">FOURTH KALIMA 2</string>
    <string name="dua">DU\'A</string>
    <string name="dua_allahummainni_zalamtunafsi_pronounce">ALLAHUMMA INNI ZALAMTU NAFSI ZULMAN KATHIRAW-WA INNAHU LA YAGHFIRUDH-DHUNUBA ILLA ANTA FAGHFIRLI MAGHFIRATAM-MIN `INDIKA WARHAMNI. INNAKA ANTAL GHAFURUR-RAHIM.</string>
    <string name="dua_allahummainni_zalamtunafsi_meaning">\"O Allah! I have wronged (oppressed) myself with many wrongs. And there are none who can forgive sins besides You. Forgive me with Your forgiveness. Have mercy upon me. You alone are the All-forgiving, the All-merciful\".</string>
    <string name="dua_to_muzdalifa">DU\’A TO MUZDALIFAH</string>
    <string name="dua_to_muzdalifa_pronounce">ALLAHUMMA ILAYKA AFADTU WA FI RAHMATIKA RAGHIBTU WA MIN SAKHATIKA RAHIBTU WA MIN ADHHBIKA ASHFAQTU FAQBAL NUSUKI WA AAZIM AJRI WA TAQABBAL TAWBATI WARHAM TAZARRUI WASTAJIB DU`AI WA A`ZINI SULI.</string>
    <string name="dua_to_muzdalifa_meaning">\"O Allah! To You I turn. To (enter) Your mercy I am eager. Your anger I dread. From Your punishment I am fearful. Accept my sacrifice, and increase my reward. Accept my repentance and have mercy on my sorry state. Accept my du`a and grant me my request\".</string>
    <string name="dua_bismillahi_allahu_akbar_pronounce">BISMILLAHI ALLAHU AKBAR</string>
    <string name="dua_bismillahi_allahu_akbar_meaning">“In the Name of Allah, Allah is the Greatest”.</string>
    <string name="dua_before_slaughtering">DU’A BEFORE SLAUGHTERING</string>
    <string name="dua_before_slaughtering_pronounce">INNI WAJ-JAHTU WAJHIYA LIL-LADHI FATARAS SAMAWATI WAL ’ARDHA HANIFAW WA MA ANA MINAL MUSHRIKIN. INNA SALATI WA NUSUKI WA MAH YAYA WA MAMATI LILLAHI RABBIL `ALAMIN. LA SHARIKA LAH. WA BI-DHALIKA UMIRTU WA ANA MINAL MUSLIMIN. ALLAHUMMA TAQABBAL MINNI HADHAN NUSUKA WAJ-`ALHU QURBANAN LI WAJ-HIKA WA `AZ-ZIM ’AJR `ALAYHA.</string>
    <string name="dua_before_slaughtering_meaning">\"I turn to firmly face the creator of the heavens and earth, in this state that I am not of the polytheists. Indeed my salaah and sacrifice, and my living and dying are solely for Allah, the Lord of the worlds, who has no equal. This is what I have been ordered and I am a Muslim (I submit my will to this). O Allah! Accept from me my sacrifice and make it a means of close proximity to You. (O Allah!) Increase my rewards for it\".</string>
    <string name="dua_while_slaughtering">DU’A WHILE SLAUGHTERING</string>
    <string name="dua_for_halaqa_or_qasr">DU’A FOR HALAQ OR QASR</string>
    <string name="dua_for_halaq_or_qasr_pronounce">ALHAMDU LILLAHI `ALA MA HADANA AL-HAMDU LILLAHI `ALA MA AN-`AMA BIHI `ALAYNA ALLAHUMMA HA-DHIHI NASIYATI FATAQABBAL MINNI WAGH-FIRLI DHUNUBI ALLAHUM-MAGHFIRLI WA LIL MUHAL-LIQINA WAL MUQAS-SIRIN YA WASI-`AL MAGHFIRAH. AMIN</string>
    <string name="dua_for_halaq_or_qasr_meaning">\"All praise be to Allah, as it is He, Who has guided us. All praise be to Allah who has bestowed His favour upon us. O Allah! I offer my subservience, accept it from me. Forgive my sins! O Allah! Forgive all who those who shave their heads and those who trim their hair. O He whose mercy is encompassing\".</string>
</resources>
