<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="types_of_hajj">Types of Hajj</string>
    <string name="there_are_three">There are following three types of Hajj:</string>
    <string name="types_of_hajj_desc">1.<b>Qiraan</b>: \nThe pilgrim wears the Ihraam with the intention of performing both Umrah and Hajj together.The pilgrim, on arriving in Makkah, first performs Umrah followed by Hajj in the same Ihraam. This is difficult but more rewarding.\n\n 2.<b>Tamattu</b>:\n The pilgrim wears Ihraam with the sole intention of Umrah. After its completion, the Ihraam is removed and another Ihraam is worn before 8th Dhul Hijjah for Hajj.\n\n 3.<b>Ifraad</b>:\n The pilgrim, intending Hajj only, enters the state of Ihraam. He does not wish to combine it with Umrah. </string>
    <string name="hajj_qiraan">HAJJ QIRAAN</string>
    <string name="one_must_wear"><b>1.</b> One must wear the Ihraam and enter it’s state, with the intention of performing both Umrah and Hajj upon or prior to reaching the Meeqat. One must perform Umrah first, thereafter Hajj. </string>
    <string name="upon_arriving_in"><b>2.</b>Upon arriving in Makkah, one should then proceed to Al Masjidul Haram and perform Umrah.\nFollow the section on Tawaaf and Sa’i in the section of "Umrah".</string>
    <string name="masalah_after_umrah_one_must_not_shave"> <u>Mas’alah:</u><font color="#ff0000">After Umrah one must not shave or trim the hair , or assume that one is no longer in Ihraam after Umrah.</font></string>
    <string name="after_this_umrah"><b>3</b>. After this Umrah, perform a second Tawaaf. This second Tawaaf is Tawaaful Qudum which is Sunnah. Follow this with Sa’i once again. This is the Sa’i for Hajj.\n\n <b>Mas’alah</b>: If one chooses to perform Sa’i of Hajj after this Tawaaf, then this Tawaaf needs to be performed with Idhtiba (keeping the right shoulder uncovered) in all seven circuits and Ramal in the first three only. Sa’i of Hajj can also be performed later, after Tawaafuz Ziyarah, but in Hajj Qiraan, it is preferable after Tawaaful Qudum.</string>
    <string name="now_one_remains"><b>4</b>. Now one remains in Makkah Mukarramah in the state of Ihraam. One will not adopt another Ihraam for Hajj.\n\n <b>5</b>. Follow the guidelines for the five days of Hajj.</string>
    <string name="hajj_tamattu">HAJJ TAMATTU</string>
    <string name="one_will_wear"><b>1</b>. One will wear the Ihraam and enter into it’s state with the intention of performing Umrah, upon or prior to reaching the Meeqat. Thereafter, upon the completion of Umrah when the time for Hajj arrives, the Ihraam will have to be donned again. The intention for Ihraam will be:</string>
    <string name="after_halaq_all_requlations"><b>3</b>. After Halaq/Qasr (shaving/trimming), all regulations of Ihraam will end. One can remain in Makkah Mukarramah without Ihraam until the five days of Hajj.\n\n <b>4</b>. Now follow the guidelines of the five days of Hajj.</string>
    <string name="hajj_ifrad">HAJJ IFRAAD</string>
    <string name="you_will_enter_the_state_of_hajj"> <b>1</b>. You will enter the state of Ihraam with the intention of performing Hajj on or prior to reaching Meeqat.</string>
    <string name="masalah_if_one_choose_to_perform"><b>Mas’alah</b>: If one chooses to perform Sa’i of Hajj after this Tawaaf, then this Tawaaf needs to be performed with Idhtiba in all seven circuits and Ramal in the first three only.</string>
    <string name="masalah_sai_of_hajj"><b>Mas’alah</b>: Sa’i of Hajj for those performing Hajj Ifraad is best after Tawaafuz Ziyarah.</string>
    <string name="intention_hajj_pronounce">ALLAHUMMA INNI URIDUL HAJJA FAYASSIR HU LI WA TAQAB-BALHU MINNI</string>
    <string name="intention_hajj_meaning">O Allah! I intend Hajj. Make it easy for me and accept it from me.</string>
    <string name="intention_hajj">DU’A FOR INTENTION FOR HAJJ</string>
    <string name="now_you_will_remain"><b>3</b>. Now you will remain in Makkah Mukarramah in the state of this Ihraam for Hajj too. \n\n<b>4</b>.Now follow the guidelines for the five days of Hajj.</string>
    <string name="first_day_8th_dhul_hijjah">FIRST DAY (8th DHUL HIJJAH)</string>
    <string name="on_the_8th_dhulhijja"><b>1</b>. On the 8th Dhul Hijjah, leave for Mina after sunrise reciting Talbiyah.</string>
    <string name="if_you_are_performing"> <b>2</b>. If you are performing Hajj Tamattu, then perform ghusl, i.e. clean up, before the morning of 8th Dhul Hijjah and put on the sheets of Ihraam. Women are to wear concealing Islamic clothes. The performers of Hajj Tamattu will proceed to al Masjidul Haram and perform two Raka’at with the head covered, intending Ihraam and Hajj, with the recitation of Talbiyah.</string>
    <string name="masalah_sai_of_hajj_which_is_normnally"><b>Mas’alah</b>: Sa’i of Hajj, which is normally performed after Tawaafuz Ziyarah, may be performed at this point if desired. but, a Sa’i cannot be performed independently of Tawaaf, thus, a Nafl Tawaaf must be performed prior to the Sa’i. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: The Nafl Tawaaf before Sa’i will be performed with Idhtiba in all seven circuits and Ramal in the first three circuits only. This is the general rule, that all those Tawaaf that accompany Sa’i will be performed with Idhtiba in all seven circuits and Raml in the first three. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: A person performing Hajj Tamattu can enter into the state of Ihraam for Hajj anytime prior to the 8th Dhul Hijjah. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: It is better (Mustahab) to make the intention of Ihraam in al Masjidul Haram.</string>
    <string name="this_day"><b>2</b>. This day and night are spent in Mina, and Zuhr, to Esha and Fajr of the following day will also be read here.</string>
    <string name="masalah_it_is_desirable"><b>Mas’alah</b>: It is desirable to perform these Salaah in Mina.\n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: There are no prescribed acts of worship on this day. One should recite Talbiyah excessively, and spend every moment in whatever form of worship one wishes.</string>
    <string name="masalah_if_the_total"><b>Mas’alah</b>: If the total number of days one intends to stay in Makkah are 15 days or more, one becomes Muqim, i.e. one will perform all the Salaah during the five days of Hajj fully. If one however, stays less than 15 days in Makkah, one is instead a Musafir and will perform Qasr, i.e. perform two Raka’at Fardh of Zuhr, Asr and Esha unless performed behind a Muqim Imam. The annual Qurbani (sacrifice) of Eidul Adha is Wajib upon the Muqim (even if he be in Makkah) provided he is in possession of Nisab (threshold of Zakaah), but it is not Wajib upon the Musafir. This sacrifice can be offered anywhere by the pilgrim. Prior to departing for Hajj the instructions can also be given to others.</string>
    <string name="masalah_takbirat_of_tashriq"><b>Mas’alah</b>: The Takbirat of Tashriq should be recited from the Fajr of the 9th Dhul Hijjah to the Asr of the 13th Dhul Hijjah, even if performing Hajj.</string>
    <string name="hajj_second_day">SECOND DAY (9TH DHUL HIJJAH)</string>
    <string name="second_day_subah_sadiq">Day Two : Subah Sadiq, you are at Mina</string>
    <string name="after_sunrise"><b>1</b>. After sunrise, set off for Arafat. En route, recite Talbiyah, and engage in other forms of Ibadah.</string>
    <string name="masalah_to_leave"><b>Mas’alah</b>: To leave for Arafah prior to sunrise is against the Sunnah.</string>
    <string name="wuquf_in_arafat"><b>Mas’alah</b>: Wuquf (staying) in Arafah commences from Zawal on the 9th Dhul Hijjah and continues to Subh Sadiq of the following morning. It is Fardh to spend at least a little portion of this time in Arafah.\nTo remain in Arafah until sunset is Wajib.</string>
    <string name="dua_enrout_to_arafat">DU’A EN ROUTE TO ARAFAH</string>
    <string name="dua_enrout_to_arafat_pronounce">ALLAHUMMA ILAYKA TAWAJ-JAHTU WA `ALAYKA TAWAKKALTU WA LI WAJ-HIKAL-KARIMI ’ARADTU FAJ`AL DHAMBI MAGHFURAN WA HAJJI MABRURAN WAR-HAMNI WA LA TUKHAY-YIBNI WA BARIK LI FI SAFARI WAQDI BI`ARAFATIN HAJATI. INNAKA `ALA KULLI SHAY’IN QADIR</string>
    <string name="dua_enrout_to_arafat_meaning">\"O Allah! To You I turn and face, upon You I hold my trust and for Your exalted continence do I aspire. Make my sins, forgiven acts, and make my Hajj accepted in Your eyes. Have mercy upon me, do not fail me, and bless me in my travel (of Hajj). In Arafah fulfil my needs. You are powerful over all\".</string>
    <string name="dua_at_arafat">DU’A AT ARAFAT</string>
    <string name="kalima_4_small_pronounce">LA ILAHA ILLAL-LAHU WAHDAHU LA SHARIKA LAH. LAHUL MULKU WA LAHUL HAMDU WA HUWA `ALA KULLI SHAY’IN QADIR.</string>
    <string name="kalima_4_small_meaning">\"There is no god but Allah. He is alone, without equal. His is sovereignty and for him is all praise. He has power over all things\".</string>
    <string name="kalima_4_big_pronounce">LA ILAHA ILLAL-LAHU WAHDAHU LA SHARIKA LAH. LAHUL MULKU WA LAHUL HAMDU YUHYI WA YUMITU WA HUWA `ALA KULLI SHAY’IN QADIR</string>
    <string name="kalima_4_big_meaning">\"There is no god but Allah. He is alone, without equal. His is sovereignty and for him is all praise. He gives life and causes death. He has power over all things\".</string>
    <string name="upon_the_time_of_zuhar"><b>3</b>. Upon the time of Zuhr commencing, perform Wudhu (Ghusl if possible would be better) and perform Zuhr with Jama’ah (congregation).\n\n<b>4</b>. Thereafter re-engage in worship, reading Durud, Dhikr, Tasbih, (praises of Allah), Talbiyah and Du’a (for yourself, family and friends and the whole Ummah).\n\n<b>5</b>. Perform Asr Salaah on its time and again engage in Ibadah until sunset.</string>
    <string name="it_is_extremely"><b>Mas’alah</b>: It is extremely desirable to remain in devotion standing and facing Qiblah, with hands raised as in Du’a. It is permitted to sit and even to lie down if required, but to recline without excuse is detestable. If one tires, one may sit, and stand again once recovered.\n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: It is an act of bid’ah to climb upon Jabalur Rahmah during wuquf. Thus abstain from it.\n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: Every so often recite talbiyah.\n\n <b>Mas’alah</b>: It is prohibited, distracting and extremely detrimental for men and women to stand together.\n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: Jum’ah Salaah cannot be performed in Arafah. One must perform Zuhr, even if it is Friday.\n\n</string>
    <string name="after_sunset_leave_for">After sunset leave for Muzdalifah. Do not perform Maghrib Salaah in Arafah.</string>
    <string name="it_is_not_permissible"><b>Mas’alah</b>: It is not permissible to depart from Arafah before sunset.</string>
    <string name="to_muzdalifa">TO MUZDALIFAH</string>
    <string name="masalah_it_is_wajib"><b>Mas’alah</b>: It is wajib to perform Maghrib and Isha together in Muzdalifah (which will be at Isha time). Therefore do not perform Maghrib or Isha in Arafah or en route to Muzdalifah. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: If you arrive in Muzdalifah before the time of Isha, do not perform Maghrib until the time of Isha sets in. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: If one is delayed for any reason (e.g. getting lost) which stops one from reaching Muzdalifah before subh sadiq, then one must perform the two Salaah wherever he may be before dawn. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: The two Salaah should be read together whether you pray alone or in congregation.</string>
    <string name="in_muzdalifa">IN MUZDALIFAH</string>
    <string name="perform_maghrib_and_isha"><b>1</b>. Perform Maghrib and Isha Salaah with one Adhan and one Iqamah as soon as the time for Isha Salaah commences. First call out the Adhan and Iqamah, thereafter perform the Faraidh of Maghrib and Isha Salaah. After these two are performed in Jama’ah, Perform the Sunnah of Maghrib followed by the Sunnah and Witr of Isha individually .\n\n<b>2</b>. After Salaah, look to fulfil your other needs such as eating, drinking, toilet, etc, and endure to spend the night in Ibadah as this night is very virtuous and full of blessings.</string>
    <string name="to_remain_in_muzdalifa"><b>Mas’alah</b>: To remain in Muzdalifah until Subh Sadiq is Sunnah Mu’akkadah, and keeping occupied in Tilawah, Ibadah and Du’a is a spiritual must (albeit Mustahab is rank). \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: Women, the sick and the disabled may omit the Wuquf of Muzdalifah due to rushing and crowding.</string>
    <string name="collect_small_peasized_pebbles"><b>3</b>. Collect small pea-sized pebbles to pelt the Jamarat and put them safely. You will need a total of 49 pebbles If you are going to leave Mina after pelting the Jamarat on the 12th Dhul Hijjah, and you will need a total of 70 pebbles if you are staying over to pelt the Jamarat on the 13th Dhul Hijjah. Collect a few extra pebbles in case you miss the Jamarat during pelting.</string>
    <string name="pebbles_for_defferent_days">7  for 10th Dhul Hijjah. \n21 for 11th Dhul Hijjah . \n21 for 12th Dhul Hijjah. \n21 for 13th Dhul Hijjah. (If one stays for that day)</string>
    <string name="it_is_permissible"><b>Mas’alah</b>: It is permissible to collect pebbles from anywhere. However, one must not pick them from near the Jamarat or from any unclean place.</string>
    <string name="hajj_third_day">THIRD DAY (10TH DHUL HIJJAH)</string>
    <string name="day_three_subhsadiq">Day Three : Subh Sadiq, you are in Muzdalifa</string>
    <string name="fajr_salah_should"><b>1</b>. Fajr Salaah should be performed as soon as its time begins.</string>
    <string name="masalah_wuquf_at_muzdalifa"><b>Mas’alah</b>: Wuquf at Muzdalifah is compulsory (Wajib), its time commences with Subh Sadiq and ends with sunrise. If one spends even a little time in Muzdalifah, he will be freed of the obligation. However, it is preferrable to stay until just before sunrise. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: If one departed from Muzdalifah before Subh Sadiq or arrived there after sunrise, he will not be freed of this obligation. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: Eid Salaah is not Wajib upon the pilgrims.</string>
    <string name="try_to_remain"><b>2</b>. Try to remain busy in Ibadah at Muzdalifah until just before the sun rises. Whilst there stand and face the Qiblah engaged in Ibadah.</string>
    <string name="just_before_sunrise"><b>1</b>. Just before sunrise (2&#8211;3 minutes), leave for Mina reciting Talbiyah, Dhikr, etc. \n\n<b>2</b>. When you reach Mina fulfil the following duties: \n\n<b>a</b>. Pelting only the large Shaytan (Rami). (Wajib) \n<b>b</b>. Animal sacrifice (Nahr). (Wajib) \n<b>c</b>. Shaving or trimming (Halaq or Qasr). (Wajib) \n<b>d</b>. Tawaafuz ziyarah. (Fardh, in Makkah)</string>
    <string name="important_if_performing_hajj"><b>IMPORTANT</b>: If performing Hajj Qiraan or Tamattu, to keep the order of Rami, Nahr and Halaq/Qasr is Wajib. Failure to do so will result in Dam. Do not under any circumstances neglect this order.</string>
    <string name="nahr_is_not_wajib"><b>Mas’alah</b>: Nahr is not Wajib for those performing Hajj Ifraad, it is Mustahab. They can shave their heads as soon as the Rami has been completed. If they wish to perform the Mustahab, they may do so before or after shaving. However, it is Mustahab to follow the same order.</string>
    <string name="the_duties_of">The duties of the 10th Dhul Hijjah (i.e. The third day of Hajj) are described with full detail here.</string>
    <string name="pelting_only">1. Pelting only the large Shaytan (Rami). (Wajib)</string>
    <string name="on_this_day">On this day one will throw seven pebbles at only the Jamaratul Uqba (large Shaytan). The largest Jamarah is the one that is furthest away from Masjidul Khayf.</string>
    <string name="masalah_it_is_an_act_of_bidah"><b>Mas’alah</b>: It is an act of Bid’ah (innovation) to pelt the other two Jamarah on this day.</string>
    <string name="when_to_perform_rami">WHEN TO PERFORM RAMI</string>
    <string name="rami_on_10th_can_be_performed">Rami on the 10th can be performed from Subh Sadiq of the 10th until Subh Sadiq of the 11th. But not all times hold the same virtue. Below one can see which times are most appropriate. \n\n(1) Makruh \u0020(disliked)  \u0020\u0020\u0020from Subh Sadiq to Sunrise \n\n(2) Masnun (preferred) \u0020from Sunrise \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020 to Zawal \n\n(3) Mubah \u0020\u0020(permitted) from Zawal \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020to Sunset \n\n(4) Makruh \u0020(disliked)  \u0020\u0020\u0020from Sunset \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020to Subh Sadiq</string>
    <string name="masalah_women_infants_and_the_sick"><b>Mas’alah</b>: Women, infants, and the sick/disabled may perform Rami at any time without fear of it being Makruh. It is better for them to choose such a time (e.g. late night) when it is less crowded.</string>
    <string name="important_note_one_must_try"><b>IMPORTANT NOTE</b>: One must try to perform Rami in the Masnun (failing which, the Mubah) time. But due to the crowds it is almost impossible to do so without harming one’s self or others. It is thus, advisable to perform Rami before Maghrib in Mubah time. If one also finds the crowd overwhelming at that time, then the healthy men may complete their obligation; leaving the women and sick to perform it afterwards, whenever it is convenient, as long as it is before Subh Sadiq.</string>
    <string name="how_to_perform_rami">HOW TO PERFORM RAMI</string>
    <string name="reciting_talbiya_approach"><b>1</b>. Reciting Talbiyah, approach the large Shaytan, in such a way that absolutely no inconvenience is caused to others, one should stand with Masjidul Khayf to the right and Makkah to the left. \n\n<b>2</b>. One by one, holding each pebble between index finger and thumb of the right hand, throw all seven. Reciting the Du’a each time;</string>
    <string name="dua_while_stoning">DU’A WHILE STONING</string>
    <string name="masalah_whilst_performing_rami"><b>Mas’alah</b>: Whilst performing Rami (when preparing to throw) stop reciting the Talbiyah. Any other Du’a or Dhikr may be recited instead. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: If all pebbles are thrown together (i.e. in one go), it will be counted as one pebble only. And a further six pebbles must be thrown to complete Rami or else Dam will be necessary. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: If the pebbles land near the pillar, without hitting it, the Rami will still be valid; but if it lands further away, it will be invalid (i.e. If not within the boundary wall around the pillar). \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: While throwing, raise the right arm to such a height that the armpit becomes visible/open. Mas’alah: There is no prescribed Du’a after pelting the large Shaytan.</string>
    <string name="important_whoever_is_able_to_reach"><b>Important</b>: Whoever is able to reach the Jamarat by any means and there is no threat of severe illness or injury, it is necessary for them to pelt the Shaytan themself. It is not permissible for them to appoint anyone else to do so on their behalf. If however one cannot walk to the Jamarat and there is no feasible means of conveyance, then only can someone pelt on one’s behalf, with one’s instruction. Many people perform Rami on behalf of others without a valid Shar’i reason. In such cases, the Rami, for the person who hasn’t performed it in person, is invalid and Dam becomes Wajib. Women and the disabled have no excuse. They can perform it after Isha Salaah.</string>
    <string name="masalah_the_rush_is_not"><b>Mas’alah</b>: The rush is not a Shar’i excuse to avoid performing Rami in person.</string>
    <string name="nahr">2. NAHR</string>
    <string name="after_the_rami">1. After the Rami, one must sacrifice an animal.</string>
    <string name="masalah_this_sacrifice"><b>Mas’alah</b>: This sacrifice is known as Damush-Shukr and is Wajib upon those performing Hajj Qiraan or Tamattu and Mustahab for those performing Hajj Ifraad.</string>
    <string name="masalah_if_performing_hajj_qiraan"><b>Mas’alah</b> : If performing Hajj Qiraan or Tamattu, one must have the intention that one’s sacrifice is Damush-Shukr, otherwise it will not suffice. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: It is better to perform the slaughter one’s self. If unable for whatever reason, then it is Mustahab to witness the slaughtering.\nIt is also Mustahab to eat from, one’s own sacrificial meat.</string>
    <string name="when_to_perform_nahr">WHEN TO PERFORM NAHR</string>
    <string name="the_sacrifice_can_take">The sacrifice can take place at any time after Rami, as long as it is done before the sunset of 12th Dhul Hijjah. If performing Hajj Qiraan or Tamattu one can not shave one’s head until the slaughtering has been performed.</string>
    <string name="halaq_and_or_qasr">3. HALAQ AND/OR QASR</string>
    <string name="after_the_sacrifice"><b>1</b>. After the sacrifice one should shave or trim their hair. This should be done facing the Qiblah and preferably starting with the right hand side.\nTo trim slightly more than an inch from the end of the plaits is sufficient for women. To shave the head is haram for them.</string>
    <string name="masalah_it_is_wajib_to_shave"><b>Mas’alah</b>: It is Wajib to shave or trim a quarter of your head to come out of Ihraam, but it is necessary to shave the rest of your head as to keep it in accordance to Islamic requirement \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: Qasr means to trim at least an inch of every hair. If one’s hair is already shorter than an inch, then shaving it is necessary.</string>
    <string name="masalah_if_one_has_completed_the_rites"><b>Mas’alah</b>: If one has completed the rites of Hajj, which must be performed before Halaq, then he is allowed to shave his own head. He may also shave another Muslim’s hair when in this situation.</string>
    <string name="with_this_the_restriction_of_ihram"><b>2</b>. With this the restrictions of Ihraam end. Besides the prohibition of sexual relationship. This will only be permitted upon completion of Tawaafuz Ziyarah.</string>
    <string name="tawafuz_ziyarah">4. TAWAAFUZ ZIYARAH</string>        
    <string name="after_halaq_qasr_perform_the"><b>1</b>. After Halaq/Qasr perform the Tawaafuz Ziyarah which is a Fardh of Hajj. Du’a is the same as in regular Tawaaf.</string>
    <string name="if_after_tawaful_qudum"><b>Mas’alah</b>: If, after Tawaaful Qudum (of those performing Hajj Qiraan or Ifraad) or after the wearing the Ihraam of Hajj (of those performing Hajj Tamattu), Sa’i had already been performed, then it need not be repeated. The Tawaaf will then be performed without Ramal and Idhtiba. If Sa’i was not previously performed, then one should adopt Ramal in the first three circuits and (if still wearing the sheets of Ihraam) perform Idhtiba in all seven circuits.</string>
    <string name="when_to_perform_tawafuzziyarah">WHEN TO PERFORM TAWAAFUZ ZIYARAH</string>
    <string name="tawafuzziyarah_can_be_performed">Tawaafuz Ziyarah can be performed from Subh Sadiq on the 10th Dhul Hijjah and must be performed by sunset on 12th. To perform it on the 10th Dhul Hijjah, if possible, is more virtuous.</string>
    <string name="masalah_to_perform_tawaafuzziyarah"><b>Mas’alah</b>: To perform Tawaafuz Ziyarah before sunset of the 12th is Wajib. Further delay will result in Dam becoming incumbent. A menstruating woman must delay her Tawaaf, until the bleeding ends. In this instance, she will not be liable to give Dam.</string>
	<string name="note_it_is_better_for_women"><b>NOTE</b>: It is better for women, the elderly, etc, to delay this Tawaaf until the 11th or 12th Dhul Hijjah. But, if one does go for Tawaaf on the 12th Dhul Hijjah, try to return to Mina before Zuhr. Otherwise the traffic to reach Mina (for Rami) will be overwhelming.</string>
	<string name="masalah_tawaafuzziyarah_may_be_performed"><b>Mas’alah</b>: Tawaafuz ziyarah may be performed at any time after Arafah. However, it is Sunnah to perform it after Halaq/Qasr. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: If one performed Tawaafuz Ziyarah before Halaq, the restrictions of Ihraam will not be lifted until the performance of Halaq.</string>
	<string name="important_tawafuzziyarah_is_a_fardh"><b>Important</b>: Tawaafuz Ziyarah is a Fardh, the omission of which will render Hajj incomplete. A menstruating woman may delay it, but its performance will not be waived (or allowed to be disregarded). If she returns home without performing it, her Hajj will remain incomplete and sexual relationship will remain Haram until she returns to Makkah and performs it, there is no time limit to this.</string>
	<string name="offer_two_rakat_make_dua"><b>1</b>. Offer two Raka’at, make du’a at the Multazam if possible then go to the well of Zamzam and drink from its water, again only if possible. \n\n<b>2</b>. Perform Sa’i. (If Sa’i was performed prior to this, it need not be repeated.) \n\n<b>3</b>. Thereafter return to Mina.</string>
	<string name="masalah_it_is_sunnah"><b>Mas’alah</b>: It is a Sunnah of the Prophet r to spend these nights in Mina, it is Makruh to spend them elsewhere.</string>
	<string name="hajj_fourth_day">FOURTH DAY (11TH DHUL HIJJAH)</string>    
	<string name="day_four_you_are">Day Four : You are in Mina</string>
	<string name="the_only_action_to_be"> The only action of Hajj to be performed today is Rami, which remains Wajib. Read same Du’as as in the first Rami. One must throw seven pebbles separately at each of the three Jamarat.</string>
	<string name="masalah_the_order_of_rami"><b>Mas’alah</b>: The order of Rami (first the small, then the middle, and finally the large) is a Sunnah. Again precaution and safety dictate that they be performed in the order of the flow of pilgrims to avoid injury.</string>
    <string name="rami_of_the_11th_and_12th">Rami on the 11th and 12th can be performed from Zawal of that day until Subh Sadiq of the next day. But again, not all times hold the same virtue. Below one can see which times are most appropriate.\n\n(1) Masnun \u0020\u0020(preferred) from Zawal \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020to Sunset \n\n(2) Makruh \u0020\u0020\u0020(disliked)  \u0020\u0020\u0020from Sunset \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020to Subh Sadiq</string>
    <string name="important_rami_is_not_permissible"><b>Important</b>: Rami is not permissible before Zawal on the 11th and 12th Dhul Hijjah. It will be invalid and will have to be redone.</string>
	<string name="approach_the_small_shaytan"><b>1</b>. Approach the small Shaytan i.e. the one nearest to Masjidul Khayf, \n\n<b>2</b>. Throw all seven pebbles, individually, reciting the same Du’a each time. \n\n<b>3</b>. After the throwing, move a little to the side, if time and crowd permit, face Qiblah supplicate with hands raised. Praise and glorify Allah I, recite Durud and make Du’a for approximately two minutes. \n\n<b>4</b>. Approach the middle Shaytan and repeat steps 1-3. \n\n<b>5</b>. Thereafter stone the large Shaytan, but do not make Du’a after it. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: The Du’a is Sunnah, only after the Rami of the small and the middle Shaytan. \n\n<b>6</b>. Return to camp and spend the day in worship and the night in Mina.</string>
	<string name="hajj_fifth_day">FIFTH DAY (12TH DHUL HIJJAH)</string>   
	<string name="the_procedures_of_this_day">The procedures of this day are identical to the fourth day.</string>
	<string name="masalah_if_one_does_not_leave_mina"><b>Mas’alah</b>: If one does not leave Mina before sunset of the 12th, but does before Subh Sadiq of the 13th, then it is Makruh to leave without Rami (pelting) of the 13th Dhul Hijjah. In this case it is Sunnah to pelt the Jamarat the following day, and it is permissible to leave Mina. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: If however, one did not leave Mina before Subh Sadiq of the 13th Dhul Hijjah, then it is Wajib to perform Rami. The omission of which, will result in Dam</string>
	<string name="important_it_is_thought"><b>IMPORTANT</b>: It is thought by people that Mina must be left before sunset of the 12th Dhul Hijjah, otherwise the Rami of the following day will become Wajib. This is not correct. Rami of the following day will only become Wajib if one stays in Mina after Subh Sadiq of 13th Dhul Hijjah (even if by a minute). People misunderstand this, and try to leave Mina before sunset and in their rush, they either pelt the Jamarat before Zawal (which is invalid altogether) or they wait in the severe heat for hours on end, just so they can perform Rami upon Zawal, and leave Mina before sunset. In this way, they place themselves in danger as well as difficulty, and not only themselves but also those under their care. This harming of themselves and of others is Haram. Practice patience and fulfil this obligation, preferably after Asr. If need be, one may delay Rami until after Maghrib. As long as one leaves Mina before Subh Sadiq, no extra duty becomes Wajib. \n\n<b>NOTE</b>: People, on their way back to Makkah may be held up and do not perform Maghrib Salaah. One must perform Maghrib wherever one may be, and upon return to Makkah immediately perform Isha.</string>
	<string name="hajj_sixth_day">SIXTH DAY (13TH DHUL HIJJAH)</string>   
	<string name="rami_of_the_13th_dhul_hijjah">Rami of the 13th Dhul Hijjah is not Wajib for the completion of Hajj. It is however much more rewarding to pelt on this day as well. \n\nIf one has decided to pelt the Shaytan on the 13th also, then the procedure and timing is identical to that of the previous days. \n\nWith the clemency of Allah, the  rites of Hajj are  complete.\nMake Du’a that Almighty Allah accepts the Hajj and showers His blessings one and all.</string>
	<string name="tawaful_wida">TAWAAFUL WIDA</string>
	<string name="tawafulwida_my_be_performed">Tawaaful wida may be performed any time after Tawaafuz Ziyarah it is however preferable to perform it just before departure. \n\n<b>1</b>. When one must depart from Makkah Mukarramah, perform tawaaful wida, which is <b><u>Wajib</u></b>. \n\n<b>2</b>. As with all Tawaafs two Raka’at Salaah should be read preferably behind Maqam Ibrahim and then go to the well of Zamzam and facing Qiblah drink from its water in three sips.</string>
	<string name="after_drinking_water"><b>3</b>. After drinking water, try to get to the Multazam and praise Allah and make Du’a for as long as possible without causing difficulty to anyone.</string>
	<string name="after_dua_make_istilam"><b>4</b>. After Du’a, make Istilam of al Hajarul Aswad. A person may experience sadness or euphoria, both are commendable. and depart with a heart filled with longing to return to these sacred sites.</string>
	<string name="masalah_if_one_returns_without_performing"><b>Mas’alah</b>: If one returns home without performing Tawaaful Wida, then one will have to give Dam. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: If a Nafl Tawaaf was performed after Tawaafuz Ziyarah, then it will suffice as Tawaaful Wida even if Niyyah of Tawaaful Wida was not made. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: Tawaaful Wida is forgiven for menstruating women and even for those who are in post-natal bleeding, as it is impermissible for them to enter the Masjid in this state. \n\n<b>Mas’alah</b>: Even after Tawaaful Wida, a pilgrim can re-enter al Masjidul Haram for Salaah or Tawaaf or even Umrah.</string>
</resources>


