<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="umrah_first">Umrah (the ‘minor Hajj’) . Is a Sunnah and can be performed anytime of the year except for the five days of Hajj . During this time, it is makruh tahrimi to perform Umrah.</string>
    <string name="virtues_of_umrah">VIRTUES OF UMRAH</string>
    <string name="farz_act_umrah">FARDH ACTS OF UMRAH</string>
    <string name="umrah">UMRAH</string>
    <string name="virtues_of_umrah_desc"><b>1</b>. One Umrah is a cleanser for the sins committed between it and another Umrah. (Bukhari, Muslim)\n2. To perform one Umrah in Ramadhan is equivalent to a Hajj . In another narration, it is equivalent to Hajj performed with the prophet.(Muslim)\n3. The performers of Hajj and Umrah are representatives (of the order) of Allah I . If they call Him, He answers them and if they seek His F orgiveness He F orgives them. (Ibn Majah)</string>
    <string name="farz_act_umrah_desc"><b>1</b>. Ihraam (i.e. The garments, with niyyah and talbiyah).\n<b>2</b>. Tawaaf (with niyyah).\n <b>The wajib acts of Umrah are</b>:\n<b>1</b>. Sa’i (walking between Safa and Marwah).\n<b>2</b>. Halaq or Qasr .</string>
    <string name="prior_to_departure">PRIOR TO DEPARTURE</string>
    <string name="prior_to_departure_desc"><b>1</b>. Before leaving, perform two raka’at nafl in one’s own home. On completing the two raka’at, firstly thank Allah for the favour which He has bestowed upon us by granting us the understanding and the opportunity to perform this duty.\n\n<b>2</b>. Thereafter, one must make du’a to Allah, and ask Him to make the journey easy, and to make it full of benefits and blessings, and that He keeps you safe from the evil of Shaytan and nafs. Also make du’a that He gives one the opportunity to use one’s time in those actions which will bring His Pleasure and that He accepts the Umrah.\n\n<b>3</b>. Now starts the journey. Throughout this journey one must perform the five fardh Salaah regularly and punctually . W e all must ensure that we do not cause harm or difficulty to anyone. But rather, one should be of assistance to any needy person, and not waste time in futile pursuits. Remember to spend as much time as possible in learning, teaching, worship and remembrance of Allah I as this is the place for it.</string>
</resources>
