<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="umrah_first">Umrah (the ‘minor Hajj’) . Is a Sunnah and can be performed anytime of the year except for the five days of Hajj . During this time, it is makruh tahrimi to perform Umrah.</string>
    <string name="virtues_of_umrah">VIRTUES OF UMRAH</string>
    <string name="farz_act_umrah">FARDH ACTS OF UMRAH</string>
    <string name="umrah">UMRAH</string>
    <string name="virtues_of_umrah_desc"><b>1</b>. One Umrah is a cleanser for the sins committed between it and another Umrah. (Bukhari, Muslim)\n2. To perform one Umrah in Ramadhan is equivalent to a Hajj . In another narration, it is equivalent to Hajj performed with the prophet.(Muslim)\n3. The performers of Hajj and Umrah are representatives (of the order) of Allah I . If they call Him, He answers them and if they seek His F orgiveness He F orgives them. (Ibn Majah)</string>
    <string name="farz_act_umrah_desc"><b>1</b>. Ihraam (i.e. The garments, with niyyah and talbiyah).\n<b>2</b>. Tawaaf (with niyyah).\n <b>The wajib acts of Umrah are</b>:\n<b>1</b>. Sa’i (walking between Safa and Marwah).\n<b>2</b>. Halaq or Qasr .</string>
    <string name="prior_to_departure">PRIOR TO DEPARTURE</string>
    <string name="prior_to_departure_desc"><b>1</b>. Before leaving, perform two raka’at nafl in one’s own home. On completing the two raka’at, firstly thank Allah for the favour which He has bestowed upon us by granting us the understanding and the opportunity to perform this duty.\n\n<b>2</b>. Thereafter, one must make du’a to Allah, and ask Him to make the journey easy, and to make it full of benefits and blessings, and that He keeps you safe from the evil of Shaytan and nafs. Also make du’a that He gives one the opportunity to use one’s time in those actions which will bring His Pleasure and that He accepts the Umrah.\n\n<b>3</b>. Now starts the journey. Throughout this journey one must perform the five fardh Salaah regularly and punctually . W e all must ensure that we do not cause harm or difficulty to anyone. But rather, one should be of assistance to any needy person, and not waste time in futile pursuits. Remember to spend as much time as possible in learning, teaching, worship and remembrance of Allah I as this is the place for it.</string>

    <!-- <string name="ihram_desc_1"><b>1</b>. Prior to entering the Miqat, try to perform ghusl, otherwise wudhu will suffice.Thereafter,wear the Ihraam,two white sheets, one for the upper and one for the lower part of the body. At this point, men may apply itr (perfume). The women should keep all their body covered in their normal (Islamic) clothing, except the face.\n\n <b>2</b>. With the head covered Perform two raka’at nafl salaah with the intention of ihraam. Recite Surah Al Kafirun in the first raka’at and Surah Al Ikhlas in the second raka’at, it is not necessary to read these particular verses, but traditions have recorded that the prophet (pbuh) had read them at this particular moment. <b>3</b>. On completing the two raka’at, remove the headgear and make niyyah of Umrah saying:</string> -->
    <string name="ihram_desc_1">Prior to entering the Miqat, try to perform ghusl, otherwise wudhu will suffice.Thereafter,wear the Ihraam,two white sheets, one for the upper and one for the lower part of the body. At this point, men may apply itr (perfume). The women should keep all their body covered in their normal (Islamic) clothing, except the face.</string>
    <string name="niyyah_making">With the head covered perform two raka’at nafl salaah with the intention of Ihraam. Recite Surah Al Kafirun in the first raka’at and Surah Al Ikhlas in the second raka’at, it is not necessary to read these particular verses, but traditions have recorded that the prophet (pbuh) had read them at this particular moment.\nOn completing the two raka’at, remove the headgear and make niyyah of Umrah saying:</string>
    <string name="enter_iharam_state">The state of Ihraam is entered by the following:\n<b>(1)</b> Making niyyah.\n<b>(2)</b> Recitating of talbiyah.</string>
    <string name="ihram_niyyah">EHRAM NIYYAH</string>
    <string name="dua_umrah_niyyat">ALLA HUMMA INNI URIDUL UMRATA FAYAS-SIRHA LI WA TAQABBALHA MINNI.</string>
    <string name="umrah_niyyat">UMRAH NIYYAH(Intention)</string>
    <string name="umrah_niyyat_meaning">“O Allah, I intend to perform Umrah. Make it easy for me and accept it from me”.</string>
    <string name="dua_after_niyyah">DU’A FOR INTENTION FOR HAJJ AND UMRAH</string>
    <string name="dua_after_niyyah_pronounce">ALLAHUMMA INNI URIDUL UMRATA WAL HAJJA FAYASSIR HUMA LI WA TAQABALHUMA MINNI, LABBAYKA BIHAJJATIW WA UMRATIN.</string>
    <string name="dua_after_niyyah_meaning">"O Allah! I intend Umrah and Hajj. Make them easy for me and accept them from me. I am present for Hajj and Umrah".</string>
    <string name="dua_after_salatul_ihram">DU’A AFTER SALAATUL IHRAM</string>
    <string name="dua_after_salatul_ihram_pronounce">ALLAHUMMA INNI AS ALUKA RIDAKA WAL JANNATA WA A UDHUBIKA MIN GHADABIKA WANNAR.</string>
    <string name="dua_after_salatul_ihram_meaning">"O Allah! I seek Your pleasure and heaven. And I seek Your refuge from Your anger and the Fire".</string>
    <string name="talbiyah">TALBIYA</string>
    <string name="talbiyah_instr">Then read the following du’a (known as <b>TALBIYAH</b>) thrice.\n\n(<u>Men</u> should recite these words <u>aloud</u>, and <u>women</u> should do so <u>softly</u>)</string>
    <string name="talbiyah_pronounce">LABBAYK. ALLAHUMMA LABBAYK. LABBAYKA LA SHARIKA LAKA LABBAYK. INNAL HAMDA WAN-NIMATA LAKA WAL MULK. LA SHARIKA LAK. </string>
    <string name="talbiyah_meaning">“Here I am at Your Service, O Lord, here I am. Here I am, no partner do You have, here I am. Truly, the Praise and the Favour is Yours, and the Sovereignty. No partner do You have”.</string>
    <string name="now_recite">Now, recite DURUD and continue making DU’A for as long as possible.</string>
    <string name="ihram_impermissible">IMPERMISSIBLE ACTS WHILST IN IHRAAM</string>
    <string name="ihram_impermissible_text"><b>1</b>. It is strictly prohibited to indulge in kissing, embracing, sexual intercourse and even talking about sex. Refrain from all those acts which are within this classification. \n\n<b>2</b>. It is prohibited and even more harmful to indulge in those acts which Allah I has ordained Haram e.g. Foul or dirty language, sin, fighting, etc. \n\n<b>3</b>. It is Haram to hunt animals or to even help anyone perform this act; even the killing of an ant or even a louse is prohibited. \n\n<b>4</b>. One must refrain from using scents, perfumes, perfumed oils, soaps, shampoos or any items of fragrance; on the body and even the clothes. \n\n<b>5</b>. It is prohibited to shave or trim hair from any part of the body; it is also prohibited to clip the nails. \n\n<b>6</b>. It is impermissible for men to use sewn or stitched clothes. \n\n<b>7</b>. It is prohibited for men to wear any such footwear that covers the central bone of the upper part of the feet. \n\n<b>8</b>. Men must not cover their heads or faces. \n\n<b>9</b>. Women, in the presence of men, must cover their faces in such a manner that the covering does not touch it, wearing a baseball type cap under the covering can be helpful. \n\n<b>10</b>. Do not cause harm to any Muslim neither verbally nor physically.</string>
    <string name="ihram_permissible">ACTS ALLOWED WHILST IN THE STATE OF IHRAAM</string>
    <string name="ihram_permissible_text"><b>1</b>. It is permissible to use an umbrella or any object for shade, as long as it does not rest on the head.\n\n <b>2</b>. Any such item which is not clothing, provided it is for a valid reason, is permitted.\n\n <b>3</b>. It is permited to wash/change one’s garments, as well as to wash one’s hair and body without using scented soap.\n\n<b>4</b>.The natural shedding of hair due to washing is not an issue of concern.\n\n <b>5</b>. It is permissible to cover the body, including the feet while sleeping with any garment or blanket. (Do not however, cover the head or face).\n\n <b>6</b>. It is permitted to use a toothbrush/miswak to clean the teeth.\n\n <b>7</b>. There is no harm in carrying something on the head if the need arises.</string>
    <string name="dua_outside_makkah">DU’A OUTSIDE MAKKAH</string>
    <string name="dua_outside_makkah_pronounce">"ALLAHUMMA ALBALADU BALADUKA WAL BAYTU BAYTUKA JI'TU ATLUBU RAMATAKA WA ALZIMU TA'ATAKA MUTTABI`AL LI'AMRIKA RADIYAN BI QUDRATIKA MUS TASLIMAL-LI AMRIKA AS'ALUKA MAS ALATAL-MUDTARRI ILAYKA AL MUSHFIKI MIN`ADHABIKA KHA'IFAN LI`UQUBATIKA AN TASTAQBILANI BI`AFWIKA WA AN TATAJAWAZA ANNI BIRAHMATIKA WA AN TUD KHILANI JAN-NATAKA.</string>
    <string name="dua_outside_makkah_meaning">\"O Allah! This city (Makkah) is Your city. And this house (Ka’bah) is Your house. I come seeking Your mercy, and holding fast unto Your obedience, subservient to Your order, pleased with Your decree and accepting Your command. I beg of You; in the begging manner of the distressed, who dread Your punishment, and fear Your wrath; that You confront me with Your pardon, and that You encompass me with Your mercy, and that You enter me into Your (prepared) Heaven\".</string>
    <string name="upon_arrival">UPON ARRIVAL AT THE HOLY CITY</string>
    <string name="upon_arrival_inst">Upon donning the Ihraam, you should engage yourself in the remembrance of Allah I, Istighfar and recitation of the Talbiyah until you reach Makkah.\n\n <b>1</b>. Enter the holy city of Makkah with true respect and humility whilst reciting the Talbiyah.\n\n<b>2</b>.Make arrangements and immediately go to the sacred Masjid which is known as Al Masjidul Haram. Where upon enter the Masjid with utmost humility, consciousness of the Greatness of Allah I and mindfulness of the sacredness of the place.\n\n <b>3</b>. When entering the Masjid, put your right foot in the Masjid and say either of the following:</string>
    <string name="dua_entering_masjid">DU\'A ON ENTERING MASJID AL HARAM</string>
    <string name="dua_entering_masjid_pronounce">BISMILLAHI WAS-SALATU WAS-SALAMU ALA RASULIL-LAH.\nALLAHUM-MAFTA LI ABWABA RAHMATIK.</string>
    <string name="dua_entering_masjid_meaning">“In the name of Allah. May the Peace and Salutations (of Allah) be upon the Messenger of Allah. O Allah, open for me the doors of Your Mercies”.</string>
    <string name="dua_leaving_masjid">DU’A ON LEAVING AL MASJIDUL HARAM</string> 
    <string name="dua_leaving_masjid_pronounce">BISMILLAHI ALLAHUMMA SALLI ALA MUHAMMADIN, ALLAHUMMA INNI ASALUKA MIN FADLIK.</string>
    <string name="dua_leaving_masjid_meaning">\"In the name of Allah. O Allah! Send Your salutation upon Muhammad. O Allah! I ask You for Your grace\".</string>
    <string name="on_seeing_kaba">When you see Ka’bah, say the following thrice:</string>
    <string name="dua_seeing_kabah">DU\'A SEEING KABAH</string>
    <string name="dua_seeing_kabah_pronounce">ALLAHU AKBAR. LA ILAHA ILLAL-LAH</string>
    <string name="dua_seeing_kabah_meaning">\"Allah is the greatest. There are none worthy of worship but Allah\".</string>
    <string name="after_dua">Thereafter, recite Durud and make du’a whilst standing and facing the Ka’bah.</string>
    <string name="dua_on_sigting_heading">DU’A ON SIGHTING THE KA’BAH</string>
    <string name="dua_on_sigting_pronounce">"ALLAHUMMA ANTAS-SALAMU WA MINKAS-SALAMU TABARAKTA YA DHALJALAALI WAL IKRAM ALLAHUMMA ZID HADHAL BAYTA TASHRIFAW WA TA'ZIMAW WATAKRIMAW WA MAHABATAN WA ZID MAN SHAR-RAFAHU WA KARRAMAHU MIMMAN HAJJAHU AWI`TAMARAHU TASHRIFAW WA TA'ZIMAW WA TAKRIMAW WA BIRRA.</string>
    <string name="dua_on_sigting_meaning">\"O Allah! You are peace, from You comes peace, elevated are You, O Possessor of majesty and clemency. O Allah! Increase this House (Ka’bah) in dignity, honour, nobility and awe. And increase those who honour and sanctify it by performing Hajj and Umrah, in dignity, honour, nobility and piety\".</string>
    <string name="important"><b>IMPORTANT</b>: This short moment is extremely precious, as whatever Du’a is made, it is certainly accepted by Allah I. Thus lengthen the Du’a at this juncture as much as possible.\n\n One must not forget to make this Du’a:\n\n <b>“O Allah, when you take me away from this world, take me in the state of Imaan. O Allah, enter me into Jannah without any account. O Allah, accept all my du’a and keep me steadfast on Deen”</b>.\n\n One should also make Du’a for the Muslim Ummah in general at this time, that Allah! help all those who are suffering\n\n <b>Mas’alah</b>: A woman in the state of menstruation or post-natal bleeding must not enter the Masjid.</string>
</resources>